<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Set Up</title><link>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/introduction/</guid><description>Download Releases Page
Start by downloading the installation file for your platform (.exe for windows and .deb for linux). Windows users can run the .exe file and choose where the bot will be installed. Linux users will need a package manager that can run .deb files. GDebi will work for this.
Windows users will likely see a warning since Glimboi is not registered with the Windows system.
Authorization GlimBoi requires authentication to talk as a bot/streamer account.</description></item><item><title>Joining Chat</title><link>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/joiningchat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/joiningchat/</guid><description>Glimesh Channels Glimboi can join any channel on Glimesh. You can join your own or a friend. You can test your commands on the Glimboi channel.
Step 1 You must have an account authorized to join a chat. The instructions for doing so can be found here. Glimboi will speak as the account authorized.
Step 2 Click on the chat page. Click &amp;ldquo;add new&amp;rdquo;
Step 3 Enter the name of the channel that you want to join.</description></item><item><title>Custom Server</title><link>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/customserver/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://glimboi.com/docs/intro/customserver/</guid><description>Custom Instance As of July 1st, Glimesh has closed. However, all code is open source. This means that you can run your own version of Glimesh, or connect to someone elses! Glimboi will work with all current versions of Glimesh, but future changes may break this compatibility.
If you are reading this before the shutdown, Glimboi will still use the default Glimesh.tv URL.
Data Export You must export your bot data before connecting to a custom instance!</description></item></channel></rss>